John W. Warner papers MSS 10191
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
- John Warner papers (-by accession), 1970-2007; MSS 10191_by; 713 Cubic Feet Cubic foot boxes; This collection consists of 712 cubic foot boxes.
  - Defense Appropriations (Sam/Cord Sterling), 1/1/1999-12/31/2002 (Box 614)
    Nat. Guard/Reserve; Percival McCormack; Mariner's Museum USS Monitor; George Mason; Heritage Center; JW Letters; Lexington Inst.; Dear Colleagues (Pending); Dear Colleagues (Signed); CVNX Funding (2 folders); Chamberlain Hotel (3 folders); Charles Warner; CINC North; Concurrent Receipt; BRAC; FY 2003 Auth. Conf.; Future; AIPAC, etc.; VA Army and National Guard Issues: AFIP; VA Army and National Guard Issues: MTMC Ft. Eustis Issue; Fort Pickett/Blackstone Sewer Pros.; Boeing [envelope]; CTBT Stuff; Gulf War Syndrome; Korean War 50th Commemoration [accordion folder]; Korean War 50th Commemoration: Korea; Korean War 50th Commemoration: Korean War Veterans Assoc. - Legislation; Missile Defense Issues (ABM, BMDO, etc.); PNTR China [accordion folder]; Export License Articles (Control)
  - Defense and Military Appropriations (Sam/Cord Sterling), 1/1/1995-12/31/2002 (Box 615)
    Blackbird; Oceana Sensor Technology; Atlantic Research Corporation (SEQUA); Jones Group; Iridium; Medicorp Health; McDermott/BWX; Newport News Shipbuilding [accordion folder]; American Maritime Congress; Ranger Raid - Somalia, 10/1993; Alliant Techsystems; EDS, Senator John Warner Trip to Norfolk, 7/9/2001; Metro Machine; John Deere Vehicle Group, 2/21/2002 Presentation; Edenspace; John Deere [presentation folder]; Raytheon; Colonna's Shipyard; Sabtech; CSC (Computer Sciences Corporation); Davis Boat Works - Frank Wagner; APTI (Advanced Power Technologies, Inc.); DSR (Digital System Resources, Inc.); John Deere GM Meeting, 2/26; Orbital/Briar Trek; Babington; Omnisec; Lipps-Crane (John Crane-Lips); DGI (Defense Group Inc.); Noesis; Global Technology; American Shipbuilding Association; ITT Industries; Lockheed Martin [accordion folder]
  - Personal Correspondence and Foreign Relations, 1/1/1987-1/20/1997 (Box 616)
    Inauguration 1997; Personal - Navy US Naval Academy, The Museum "Henry Huddleston Rogers Ship Model Collection" [envelope]; Personal - Air Force (General) [envelope]; Personal - US Navy Memorial Foundation (Senator serves on Board) [envelope]; Personal - Photos, Incidents at Sea Agreement Negative [envelope]; Personal - Armed Serves Committee, 1989 [envelope]; Personal - Navy, Naval Aviation Museum Foundation, Inc. [envelope]; Personal - Navy, General Correspondence [envelope]; Untitled Envelope: Personal - Organizational Meeting; Personal - Senate History [envelope]; Personal - Senator/Congressmen (Former Members) [envelope]; Personal - Senate Republican Conference [envelope]; Personal - Senate Telecommunications Department, Wats Extender [envelope]; Personal - Supreme Court, Chief Justice Warren E. Burger Letter of Resignation [2 envelopes]; Personal - Supreme Court, Lewis F. Powell, Jr. (Retired Supreme Court Justice) [envelope]; Personal - Supreme Court, Bork (Nominee to Supreme Court) [envelope]; 40th Annual Shad Planking, Westfield, Virginia, 4/20/1988 [envelope]; Personal - Voting Record, 96-100 [envelope]; Personal - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies [envelope]; American Air Museum Britain; Personal - Internal Institute for Strategic Studies (IISS); Personal - CSIS Advisory Board Center for Strategic and International Studies; Personal - Military Order of the Carabao; Personal - Ditchley Foundation, New York-London; Personal - Military History; Personal - Personal Notes, Misc., 1992; Haiti; Youth Services International, Inc [presentation folder]; Intezc Committee, 1/1993; Information Package [binder]
  - Senate Committee on Armed Services Reports, 1/1/1987-12/31/1990 (Box 617)
    Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Department of Energy National Security Programs Authorization, 100th Congress, 2nd Session, Volume 1 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 101st Congress, 2nd Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 100th Congress, 1st Session, Volume 1 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 100th Congress, 2nd Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Department of Energy National Security Programs Authorization, 101st Congress, 1st Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]
  - Senate Committee on Armed Services Reports, 1/1/1987-12/31/1991 (Box 618)
    Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Hearings, 101st Congress, 1st & 2nd Sessions [2 bound volumes]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization and Department of Defense Appropriations, 102nd Congress, 1st Session [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Reports and Laws, 1st & 2nd Sessions [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization and Department of Defense Appropriations, 100th Congress, 2nd Session [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 101st Congress, 2nd Session, Volume 1 [bound volume]
  - Senate Committee on Armed Services Reports, 1/1/1987-12/31/1990 (Box 619)
    Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Department of Energy National Security Programs Authorization, 100th Congress, 1st Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 100th Congress, 1st Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Committee Prints and Activities Report, 100th Congress, 1st & 2nd Sessions, [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Nominations, 100th Congress, 1st & 2nd Sessions, [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Department of Energy National Security Programs Authorization, 101st Congress, 2nd Session [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Hearings, 100th Congress, 1st & 2nd Sessions, [3 bound volumes]
  - Senate Committee on Armed Services Reports, 1/1/1987-12/31/1990 (Box 620)
    Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Construction Authorization and Appropriations, 101st Congress, 2nd Session [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization and Department of Defense Appropriations, 100th Congress, 1st Session, [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Construction Authorization and Appropriations, 100th Congress, 1st Session, Volume 1 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Calendar, 101st Congress, 1st & 2nd Sessions [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Department of Energy National Security Programs Authorization, 100th Congress, 1st Session, Volume 1 [bound volume]
  - Senate Committee on Armed Services Reports, 1/1/1987-12/31/1990 (Box 621)
    Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Construction Authorization and Appropriations, 100th Congress, 1st Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 101st Congress, 1st Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Construction Authorization and Appropriations, 101st Congress, 1st Session, Volume 1 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization and Department of Defense Appropriations, 101st Congress, 2nd Session, [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Department of Energy National Security Programs Authorization, 100th Congress, 2nd Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Nominations, 101st Congress, 1st & 2nd Sessions, Volume 1 [bound volume]
  - Senate Committee on Armed Services Reports, 1/1/1987-12/31/1991 (Box 622)
    Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 102nd Congress, 1st Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Department of Energy National Security Programs Authorization, 102nd Congress, 1st Session [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 101st Congress, 1st Session [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization and Appropriations, 102nd Congress, 1st Session [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 100th Congress, 2nd Session, Volume 1 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Construction Authorization and Appropriations, 100th Congress, 2nd Session [bound volume]
  - Senate Committee on Armed Services Reports, 1/1/1985-12/31/1991 (Box 623)
    Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Reports and Laws, 100th Congress, 1st & 2nd Sessions, [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization, 102nd Congress, 1st Session, Volume 1 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Department of Energy National Security Programs Authorization, 101st Congress, 1st Session, Volume 1 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Construction Authorization and Appropriations, 101st Congress, 1st Session, Volume 2 [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Goldwater-Nichols Department of Defense Reorganization Act of 1986, 99th Congress, 1st & 2nd Sessions [bound volume]; Senate Committee on Armed Services Report, Military Procurement Authorization and Department of Defense Appropriations, 101st Congress, 1st Session, [bound volume]
  - Photographs, 1/1/1985-12/31/1997 (Box 624)
    Casual Pix; World Events; Pix with Congressmen/Women; Pix with World Leaders; Pix with Interns/Staff; Senator John Warner Portraits; Atoka; Charity Pix; Awards [empty]; National Events; Miscellaneous; Virginia Events; In Office Pix; On the Campaign; Events 1993; Events 1992 [empty]; Personal Pix; Hearings/Conferences
  - Photographs, 1/1/1986-12/31/1991 (Box 625)
    In Office Shots, 1990; Trips - USA; Hearings/Conferences (empty); Trips - International: 1990 El Salvador Trip; Awards, 1989; Events, 1991; Atoka; Miscellaneous; Senator John Warner - Casual (empty); Senator John Warner - with Officials/Congressmen; Campaign Photos (empty); Trips - Virginia; In Office Shots, 1991; Events, 1989; Senator John Warner with Nunn/Aspin; Maritime/Launching (empty); Campaign/Elections; In Office Shots, 1989; Awards, 1991 (empty); Senator John Warner - Singles/Press; Navy - Secretary of (empty); Awards, 1990 (empty); Newsletter; Events, 1990; Senator John Warner - with Staff/Interns
  - Photographs, 1/1/1975-12/31/1988 (Box 626)
    Trips - Virginia; Senator John Warner - with Staff/Interns; Awards, ?; Trips - USA; Events, ?; Atoka; Bicentennial Commission; Miscellaneous; Hearings/Conferences (empty); Senator John Warner - Casual; Maritime/Launching; In Office Shots, 1985; Senator John Warner - Singles/Press; Events, 1988; In Office Shots, 1987; In Office Shots, 1986 (empty); Awards, 1987; Navy/Secretary of; Awards, 1985; Awards, 1988 (empty); Senator John Warner - with Officials/Congressmen; Events, 1985; Campaign/Elections; In Office Shots, 1988; Events, 1986; Trips - International; Events, 1987; In Office Shots, ?; Awards, 1986
  - Homeland Security, FEMA, and Hurricane Katrina (Angela Stewart), 1/1/2006-12/31/2006 (Box 627)
    Isabel Relief; FEMA Issues - 2006 Flooding in VA; FEMA - Ernest, VA, 2006; Homeland [accordion folder]; Hurricane Katrina [binder]; Exhibit Book - Hurricane Katrina: The Defense Department's Role in the Response, 2/9/2006 [binder]
  - Homeland Security Hearings and Business Meetings, Commodities Markets, and Post 9/11 (Angela Stewart), 1/1/2007-9/17/2008 (Box 628)
    Oil Prices/Commodities [accordion folder]; Committee on Homeland Security and Governmental Affairs - Business Meeting, 11/14/2007 [binder]; Six Years After 9/11 - HSGAC Hearing, 9/10/2007 [binder]; Committee on Homeland Security and Governmental Affairs - Financial Speculation in Commodity Markets Witness List, 5/20/2008 [binder]; Committee on Homeland Security and Governmental Affairs - Business Meeting, 9/17/2008 [binder]; Untitled Envelope: Subcommittee on Investigations of the Committee on Homeland Security and Governmental Affairs
  - Homeland Security Hearings, Port Security, Watch List, Campus Security, and REAL ID (Angela Stewart), 1/1/2005-11/14/2007 (Box 629)
    Homeland Grant Formula - S.21, 109th Congress [binder]; Campus Security Hearing, 4/23/2007 [binder]; Nominations: Baker and Myers Hearing, 9/25/2005 [binder]; Nomination: Chertoff Hearing, 2/2/2005 [binder]; Watching of the Watch List - HSGAC Hearing, 10/24/2007 [binder]; The Future of Port Security Hearing, 4/5/2006 [binder]; Subcommittee on Oversight of Government Management, the Federal Workforce, and the District of Columbia Hearing Briefing Book - Understanding the Realities of REAL ID, 3/26/2007 [binder]; REAL ID [accordion folder]; Untitled Accordion Folder: Business Meeting, 11/14/2007
  - Education: Minority Serving Institutions, Impact Aid, Shepherd Program, and Teacher Tax (Angela Stewart), 9/28/1996-12/31/2007 (Box 630)
    Virginia and NCLB [accordion folder]; NCLB Drafts, etc. [accordion folder]; Minority Technology Act [accordion folder]; Teacher Tax [accordion folder]; Shepherd Consortium [accordion folder]; Impact Aid [accordion folder]; Pell Grants [accordion folder]; FERPA File [accordion folder]
  - Health Care: Medical Liability Reform, Mental Health Parity, and Lifespan Respite Care (Angela Stewart), 1/1/2003-7/11/2008 (Box 631)
    Medical Liability Reform: Statement/Amendment; Medical Liability Reform: Endorsement; Medical Liability Reform: Very Important Factual Info; Medical Liability Reform: Virginia Law; Medical Liability Reform: Bills, etc.; Medical Liability Reform: Parma Provision; Medical Liability Reform: Amendment; Culpepper Regional Hospital [accordion folder]; ALS [accordion folder]; Proton Beam NCI [accordion folder]; Mental Health Parity [binder]; Association Health Plans/Small Business Health Plans [accordion folder]; UVA Cancer Research - Letter to HHS [accordion folder]; Breaux-Frist; Virginia's Medicaid; Summaries/Analysis; Medicare Summary, 2003 [accordion folder]; Respite Care [accordion folder]; Medicare Bills [accordion folder]; Lifespan Respite Funding [accordion folder]
  - Energy, Environment, and Transportation (Tack Richardson), 1/1/2003-12/31/2006 (Box 632)
    Virginia Land Conservation Efforts; WMATA (Metro) (2 folders); Virginia Indians; Shenandoah Nat'l Battlefield; VCU-USFWS Rice Center (Fisheries); Rappahannock River; Potomac Nat'l Historical Scenic Trail; James River; National Scenic Byways Program Nominations - GW Parkway, Blue Ridge Parkway, Skyline Drive, Colonial Parkway; Jamestown 2007; I-81; Dulles Toll Road; Fish Hatcheries; H2Gen - Hydrogen Generation and FCV; DoD Waste Management - Brad Contact; Craney Island; Chesapeake Bay Gateways; Chesapeake Bay Farm Bird Issues; Bussmann Aviation; Captain John Smith Chesapeake National Historic Watertrail; Charlottesville - Albemarle Airport; Yucca Mountain (Nuclear Waste Disposal); Water and Wastewater; Wild Horses; Wilderness Issues; Wind Energy - Offshore and Highland; TEA-21 Reauthorization; State Wildlife Grant Program; Roadless; Republican Policy Briefs; Renewable Energy; Pesticides; Oil and Natural Gas Stats; Ocean Issues; Natural Gas Issues; Nature Serve
  - Meeting Notes, Phone Call Log, and Background Information Files, A - N (Tack Richardson), 1/1/2004-11/20/2008 (Box 633)
    Firefighter's Issues; MARAD: Ship Disposal James River Reserve; Phone Call Logs [bundle]; Arctic National Wildlife Refuge (ANWR); Energy Bill; Drunk Driving Issues; Clean Air Rules; Amtrak; Mining Issues; Airline Pensions (United, US Air, Etc.) & Retirement Age (FAA, NATCA); National ID; Fisheries Issues; Chemical Plant Security; National Wildlife Refuge; Climate Change (Clear Skies, Climate Stewardship, Etc.); Appalachian Regional Commission (ARC); Meeting Notes, 2004-2008 [8 spiral notebooks]; Endangered Species (ESA); Forest Issues; LIHEAP (Low-Income Housing Energy Assistance Program); Indian Affairs; Arts (Issues, Funding, Etc.); Aviation in DC Area; EPW - Naming Public Facilities; Disaster Relief Information (FEMA, SBA, Etc.); Airline Flight Service; Interstate Waste; National Forests
  - Woodrow Wilson Library, Environment Issues, and STANDUP Act (Tack Richardson), 1/12/2001-6/9/2008 (Box 634)
    STANDUP Act - S.2318, 109th Congress [accordion folder]; Woodrow Wilson Presidential Library [accordion folder]; Roadless Area Conservation Act, 110th Congress [accordion folder]; Northern Neck National Heritage Area; Journey Through Hallowed Ground [accordion folder]; Dominion Power Line [accordion folder]; Green Buildings - S.506, 110th Congress [accordion folder]; Washington-Rochambeau Revolutionary Route (W3R)
  - Transportation, Environment, and Park Issues (Tack Richardson), 1/1/2005-6/30/2008 (Box 635)
    Newport News Interchange; Historic Preservation Tax Credits; Interstate 81; Rural Electric Coop Issues; New River - Wild & Scenic S.1057; Jefferson Davis Statue; Virginia Beach - Southeastern Parkway; Abingdon Courthouse Naming; Virginia Bridge Infrastructure; Tallow/Soap/Biodiesel Issue; Back Bay Facility Naming for Senator John Warner; U.S. National Slavery Museum; HOT Lanes on Beltway; Cedar Creek/Belle Grove; MARAD Issues; Davis WMATA Bill; Buffer Program (DoD); Black Bear Landfill; Dominion Lake Anna; D.C. WASA (Water and Sewer Authority); Richmond Airport; King William Reservoir; Hampton Roads SS0 Letter; Fort Belvoir; Chesapeake Bay Blue Crab; WMATA Bill (Background); Bridge Information; Appalachian Region Commission (ARC); Potomac National Scenic Trail (Fort Belvoir Issue); Primary Seat Belt; Craney Island; NOAA Norfolk Land Transfer; New River (Scenic River Bill); Shenandoah Fish Kill; Shenandoah Fish Kill; Short-Line Railroad; HRT - Norfolk Light Rail; Roanoke Valley Economic Regional Commission; Liquid Coal Information; WaterISAC (Water Information Sharing and Analysis Center) (Dear Colleague); Wallops Island; Captain John Smith National Historic Trail; FAA Reauthorization; Port of Virginia Gateway; Goshen/Lake Merriweather; Forest Service - Wind Energy Letter with Alexander & Gregg; Richmond Courthouse Naming; Potomac Riverboat - Ferry to National Harbor; Perimeter at DCA; Web Page; Offshore Drilling; Manassas Battlefield Tree-Cutting; CIT (Center for Innovative Technology); Waste to Energy; Hopper Dredge McFarland; I-73; FAMPO I-95 Fredericksburg Interchange; Westmoreland County Sewer; LIHEAP (Low Income Home Energy Assistance Program); Guns in Parks; Mt. Vernon-to-Capitol Hill Program; EPA STAG Background; U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Background; OCS Virginia Natural Gas 2008 (S.3147); King William Reservoir; Light Bulb Bill; Wolf Trap
  - Successful White House Political Appointments (Doriene Steeves), 1/1/2002-12/31/2007 (Box 636)
    41 folders of Successful Appointments, Charlie Abell to L. Donelson Wright
  - Campaign Material, 1/1/1976-12/31/2002 (Box 637)
    Eastern District of Virginia - Judgeship 2006: Rosen; 2006 U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia - Interviews: Burnett; Judgeship - Eastern District of Virginia: Bar Association - Statewide Local/Regional; Judgeship - Eastern District of Virginia [accordion folder]; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Howard C. Vick, Jr. [binder]; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: MacMahon; U.S. District Judgeship - Eastern District of Virginia [accordion folder]; 2006 U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia - Interviews: Hackman; U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia, 2005: Trindall; U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia, 2005: Hackman; Eastern District of Virginia - Judgeship 2006: O'Grady; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Press; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Apperson; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Baril; Judgeship - Eastern District of Virginia: Holm; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Beales; U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia, 2005: Cleveland; Eastern District of Virginia - Judgeship 2006: Thacher; Eastern District of Virginia - Judgeship 2006: Baker; U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia, 2005: Cahall; Judgeship - Eastern District of Virginia: Brownlee; 2006 U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia - Interviews: Cahall; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Senate Judiciary Questions; 2006 U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia - Interviews: Valentine; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Cook; U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia, 2005: Valentine, Michael; U.S. District Judgeship - Eastern District of Virginia: Miller; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Steele; 2006 U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia - Interviews: Trindal; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Rosenberg; 2006 U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia - Interviews: Zotto; U.S. District Court - Eastern District of Virginia: Novak, David; Judgeship - Eastern District of Virginia: Virginia Bar Information; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Vick; U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia, 2005: Burnett; Judgeship - Eastern District of Virginia: Summary; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Nelson; U.S. District Judgeship - Eastern District of Virginia: Sutherland; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia [accordion folder]; Eastern District of Virginia - Judgeship 2006: Somers; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Corkoran; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: Powell, Lewis, Political Recommendation, Dup File; U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia, 2005: Valentine, Zotto; U.S. Attorney - Eastern District of Virginia: McNally; 2006 U.S. Marshal - Eastern District of Virginia - Interviews: Summary Memo
  - Judgeship Deliberations (Doriene Steeves), 1/1/1996-12/31/2006 (Box 638)
    Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Gregory, Roger, 4th Circuit Court of Appeals; Virginia Judgeships, 1997; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Gorton, Slade, 9th Circuit Court of Appeals; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Burch, J. Thomas, Political Recommendation, U.S. Court of Appeals for Veterans Affairs; Fourth Circuit U.S. Court of Appeals [accordion folder]; Judges; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Grace, Michael, Political Recommendation, U.S. Tax Court; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Hagel, Larry, Political Recommendation, U.S. Court of Appeals for Veterans Claims; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Humphreys, Judge Robert, 4th Circuit Court of Appeals; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Kasold, Bruce E., Court of Federal Claims - 2004; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Schaumber, Peter, Political Recommendation, D.C. Court of Appeals; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Ross, Terry, D.C. Court of Appeals; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Colvin, John, U.S. Tax Court; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Terwilliger, George, D.C. Court of Appeals; Judgeship 4th Circuit [accordion folder]; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Kelly, Walter, Eastern District of Virginia; Judgeship 4th Circuit: Allen, Claude; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Miller, George, Political Recommendation, U.S. Court of Federal Claims; Virginia Bar Associations; Judgeships - Bush, 2000-2004: Kinser, Cynthia, 4th Circuit Court of Appeals
  - Judgeship Deliberations (Doriene Steeves), 2/1/2007-5/30/2007 (Box 639)
    U.S. District Judge for the Eastern District of Virginia, 2/2007 [2 binders]; Eastern District Judgeship, 2/2007 [accordion folder]; U.S. Court of Appeals for the Fourth Circuit Court, 5/2007 [binder]